既然我们已经完成了对应用UI的创建，
Now that we've finished build the UI for our app,
现在该考虑当应用不在前台得时候，
it's time to think about how it should operate when it's
怎么让应用操作运行的事了。安卓最有力量的一点就是
not in the foreground. One of the most powerful features of
它能让任何app运行在后台。
Android, is the ability for any app to run in the
但有更大的力量意味着更大的责任。所以你需要
background. But with great power comes great responsibility. So, you need
非常重视它是如何消耗资源的。在这门
to be very conscious of how it's consuming resources. In this
课程里，你将会学习安卓框架是如何运作后台程序的
lesson, you'll learn more about how the Android framework manages background
和即将介绍的服务类会帮助你
apps and you'll be introduced to the service class to help
实现它。你也将会学习使用同步适配器
make that happen. You'll also learn techniques for efficient
和谷歌云消息进行有效的数据转换。以及
data transfers using sync adapters and Google Cloud messaging. And
当你的app没有运行在前台得时候，
be introduced to the notification framework to send messages
如何发送信息给你的app使用者们。
to your users when your app isn't in the foreground.